嘿嘿，我是多米尼克-G，这是
hey hey I'm Dominic g and this
是深层生态系统中心
is deep ecosystem ci
深度生态系统
the deep ecosystem
是很多的项目
is a lot of projects
许多依赖深度生态系统的软件包
many packages that depend on deep
框架，用它来构建很棒的东西
frameworks use it to build awesome things
我们今天看到了很多很酷的演讲
we've seen so many cool presentations today and
所有这些都是通过beat实现的
all of that is made possible by beat
它正在快速成长
it's growing fast
为了继续繁荣发展
and to continue to thrive
我们需要一个稳定的基础来工作
we need a stable base to work with
持续集成保证了这一点
this is ensured by continuous integration
V中的每一个变化都经过测试
every change in v is tested
在V的测试和playwright上用CI构建。
with a ci build on v tests and playwright
但它仍然发生在屏幕上
but it still happened on screen
只能运行下游的测试
it's only possible to run downstream tests
周发布之后
after week was released
还是说
or is it
使用Vitacosystem ci
with vitacosystem ci
我们可以在发布前运行下游测试
we are able to run downstream tests before
我们发布杂草
we release weed
这意味着我们可以得到
and that means we get
这意味着我们可以立即得到反馈，减少下游的失败。
immediate feedback and less fails happen downstream
为了做到这一点，我们将一个典型的维护者设置自动化了
to do that we automate a typical maintainer set up
链接项目
links projects
并安装测试，然后
and installs tests and then
报告给上游项目
reports back tothe upstream project
我们还支持很多工具
we also support a lot of tools that
我们也支持很多工具，这些工具是肉体生态系统的
are the meat ecosystem
项目使用的工具，如pmpm
project use like pmpm
纱线
yarn
deno
bit lfs
并通过自定义脚本，你可以
and through custom scripts you can
基本上建立一切
basically build everything
也支持嵌套
also nesting is supported
这对于复杂的设置是很重要的，比如
which is important for complex setups like
插头和膨胀以及汗水套件
plug and swelled and sweat kit
几乎不可能一直手动运行这个程序
almost impossible to run this manually all the time
所以我们使用了一个喷气式的行动
so we use a jet up action
矩阵来并行地运行所有的测试
matrix to run all the tests in parallel
并获得预定的反馈
and get scheduled feedback
我们可以手动触发它
we can trigger it manually
感谢Softy Red的杰出贡献
and thanks to an awesome contribution by softy red
vtpr上的评论就可以了
comment on vtpr is all it takes
来测试该PR中的代码
to test the code in that PR
与大多数vdecosystem ci
with most of the vdecosystem ci
这就是
this is
我相信我们创造了
I believe we create
它是
it's
一个很好的方法来确保
a great way to ensure the
变化做他们想做的事
changes do what they intend to
而且不会产生令人不快的副作用
and don't have unpleasant side effect
我们可以在每个节拍的提交上运行它
we can run it on every beat commit
分支标签或发布的mpm rapper street上运行。
branch tag or releases on the mpm rapper street also
将报告返回到discord频道
report come back to a discord channel
这样我们就有一个地方
so we have a place
烹饪维护者和
cooking maintainers and
谈论失败，看看需要做什么
talk about fails and see what needs to be done
来解决这个问题
to fix that
而且，当推动时，我们仍然可以在本地检查出
and when push comes to show we can still check out
生态系统CI项目
ecosystem ci project locally
使用
use
好的
the nice
设置节点来分析
set node to analyze
准确地找到引入故障的漫画。
the fail and find the exact comic that introduced it
算起来，他们已经
countly they're already
许多伟大的项目
many great projects
使用生态系统CI
using ecosystem ci
但要加入自己的项目也不难
but it's not hard to add your own
只是有一点冲突而已
it's just a little bit of conflict
告诉我们你的rapo和
telling us about your rapo and
构建和测试所需的脚本，以及
the scripts needed for building and testing and
其余的都是
the rest is
剩下的就由生态系统的CI自动完成
done automatically by ecosystem ci
这不仅有利于吃，也有利于游戏
this benefits not only eat which games
减少机场和石膏的反馈
less airport and plaster feedback
而且还有更多的覆盖面
and also a lot more coverage
覆盖面也比
than would be possible by
覆盖面要比只维护单一的测试食物多得多
maintaining just a single test food
但它也有好处
but it's also benefit
它也有利于使用它的项目，因为
it also benefits the projects that use it because
你
you
在Bug进入V版之前就能及早得到通知
get notified of bugs early before
它们进入V版并
they enter a v release and
可能会影响到你的用户步骤
might hit your user step
使用码头防御系统
use a pier defendancy
或者你对更新节拍有信心，因为
or you aim confidence for updating beat because
的一致性，我已经
the consistency I already
运行并通过你的胸部套装
ran and passed your chest suit
主要的好处之一是
one of the main benefits is that
它也允许你升级
it also allows you to upgrade
到一个新的
to a new
小麦的主要版本，以更快的方式
wheat major release in faster way
因为当一致性CI在vpita上运行并且
because when a consistency ci runs on a vpita and
你参与其中
you participate it in that
升级后
upgrading after
小麦已经发布了它的最终版本
wheat has released its final version
是
is
没心没肺，单打独斗
heartless and singles
所以对于
so for
维持杂草生态系统的增长
sustaining growth in the weed ecosystem
请与我们在生态系统的CI上进行合作
please collaborate on the ecosystem ci with us
并继续发挥其威力，建立一些
and continue to be awesome and build things
我们今天甚至没有带来的东西
we don't even bring about today
非常感谢你们
thank you so much for
很棒，而且
being awesome and
也感谢Lob
also thanks lob
patak和subscriber red在肉食方面的工作。
patak and subscriber red for working on meat
生态系统CI的工作
ecosystem ci with me
还有那些可爱的人
and the lovely people
和可爱的人们提供了很棒的照片
on unspatched for providing awesome photos
这个世界击败了生态系统CI
this world beat ecosystem ci
和多米尼克感谢你的关注，再见
and Dominic thanks for watching goodbye